therehabguide.com 2015-12-06

# The Rehab Guide ® - Addiction Intake Publishing (Rehab finder)

At [The Rehab Guide](http://www.therehabguide.com/node/5) we understand the importance of protecting your privacy.  
Our **Privacy Policy** covers our treatment of personal information collected when anyone is on our site or uses the services we provide It neither addresses nor applies to individuals or third party practices over which we have no control.  
This includes but is not limited to cookies which may be used by our advertisers.

The Rehab Guide and affiliated websites only collects information pertinent to our website; as such, our stated goal is to customize your experience and let you get the most out of what we offer. To that end: The Rehab Guide will never rent or sell any of the personal information you provide.

For your security and privacy, your information is protected with a password created by you. You will always have access to your personal information and you may edit or delete it at any time. In an effort to protect children, users must be 13 years old to use our site.

 **At The Rehab Guide, information is collected in 4 ways:**

1\. By what you provide to us when you enter your registration information, which requires an email address as well as some basic information about you. You do not need to register to use our site, and if you do register you may omit certain information; however, please be aware that doing so may restrict you from enjoying the full range of our web site. If you choose to create a profile with a Sign-In Name, Bio, Recent Posts etc., The Rehab Guide makes it possible for other users to browse the site for this information.

2\. By what your computer automatically provides to us. Via our server, TheRehabGuide.com. collects your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you visit in an effort to help us administer and improve our site. Our servers use cookies to enable us to recognize your computer and facilitate use of our site. They do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information gathered by cookies with any personal information provided by you through registration. You may disable cookies from the "help" toolbar on your [Internet](http://www.therehabguide.com/icons/internet) browser.

3\. For inquiries regarding treatment or requests for our services we only use that information to find treatment, coverage and benefits for you or your client with your verbal or online form requested consent. Under certain Circumstances the information we gather from you regarding treatment is protected under the Confidentiality of Alcohol and Drug Abuse Patient Records, 42 C.F.R. Part 2, and the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 ("HIPAA"), 45 C.F.R. Pts. 160 & 164 and in those circumstances will not under any circumstances be shared without your written consent.

We will never sell, offer or give your personal information to third parties for purposes not directly related to providing you with our services. We will only use your personal information to provide the best possible services. Changes & Conditions of Use Changes or amendments to our Privacy Policy may occur now and again as warranted. However, information is always and only subject to the policy in place at the time it is collected. Should we feel the need to execute a change in the Policy, we will announce the change on our website so that our users are made aware of the change and may act accordingly.

Finally, the conditions of use (visits to our website, including the information collected, our use of that information, and any future disputes regarding issues of privacy) are subject to both this Policy in addition to our Terms of Use.

 **Funding:**  
The Rehab Guide. is a privately held company which provides [addiction](http://www.therehabguide.com/premier-rehabs/la-paloma-treatment-center) treatment Psychology, [Substance Abuse](http://www.therehabguide.com/premier-rehabs/canyon-treatment-center) Psychotherapy services Clinical evaluations and chemical dependency solutions via online search, imprint and refers the user to specific case management treatment thru referrals to our alliances network. Neither our organizations nor the editorial committee recommends or endorses a particular agency, web link, or viewpoint. The information accessed through The Rehab Guide Is provided "AS-IS," without any warranty, express or implied.

The selected web links exemplify the diversity and range of information that is available. This information is not intended to be complete, should not be used for diagnosing or treating a health problem or disease, and should not be used in place of a visit or call to your health care provider. We urge you not to disregard medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on the Internet.  
4.By Platform/Social Network - The Rehab Guide, and for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, ("we", "us", or "our") are a Platform Social Network user for Facebook, Twitter AddtoANY, ShareThis, Vimeo, Youtube, Flicker, Pinterest, Google Plus, Yahoo, Linkedin and many other social network sites ("Platform Applications") (both terms which are defined in the Social network site of your choice generally listed as (Privacy Policy). Where and if when we collect personally identifiable information from you ("Personal Information") we will deal with that information in accordance with these Terms and in particular our Privacy Policy set out HEREIN.

 **Use of Our Platform Applications / All Social networks**  
We have created connection with Social Media Platform Applications and this document (together with the documents referred to on it and the Platform Application Terms of Use (which you agreed to via the use of for Social networks) sets out the Terms on which you may make use of any Platform Applications. Please read these Terms and the associated documentation carefully before you start to use the Platform Applications. By using any of any Platform Applications, you indicate that you accept these Terms and that you agree to abide by them. If you do not agree to these Terms, please refrain from using any Social networks Platform Applications.

You the user give absolute rights by loginin to The Rehab Guide and affiliated web sites to use Photo, videos or any kind of media submitted directly or inderectly, uploaded to our server or via any other Social Media Platform Application.  
Please note that where there is a conflict between these Terms and the Platform Application Terms of Use, these Terms shall apply.  
We have endeavored to be honest and accurate about what Social networks Platform Applications do and how we use your Personal Information but, if you have any queries after reading this document, the FAQ pages and the help links in the top right corner of our Platform Application that you have a query about, please [contact us](http://www.therehabguide.com/form/contact-us) using the address at the bottom of this page.  
Information submitted by you via Social Network platforms.

We process your Personal Information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By using any of our Platform Applications, you consent to such processing and you warrant that all information provided by you is accurate.

The Facebook Platform, Janrain.com does not give us access to your e-mail address, personal website, instant messenger ID, telephone number or street address ("Contact Information") and Facebook, Twitter and other social networks will only disclose your other profile information and user images to us in accordance with the Social networks policy you have allowed to be disclosed in your privacy setting at other networks.

 **Privacy Policy.**  
Some of our Platform Applications ask you to submit Contact Information. If you choose to complete and submit forms via any Platform Applications, we will collect your Contact Information in accordance with these Terms and our Privacy Policy. If you do not want us to use you’re Contact Information, either do not use the relevant Platform Application or do not enter that information or submit the relevant form.  
Accessing any Social Network Platform Applications

Access to Platform Applications is permitted on a temporary basis, and we reserve the right to withdraw or amend the service we provide without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason any of any Social Networks Platform Applications or unavailable at any time or for any period.  
From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of the Social networks  
Platform Applications. If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any third party. We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by us, at any time, if in our opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these Terms.

You are responsible for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to any Platform Applications. Please do not allow anyone else to use or access any Social networks Platform Applications through your Facebook Account - this is against all Social networks policy. If you do so, you are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access any Social networks Platform Applications through your Social networks Account are aware of these Terms, and that they comply with them.
